http://www.asubmissivesjourney.com/privacy.html

asubmissivesjourney.com Privacy Policy
What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or mailing address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: ; To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs); To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you); To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature; To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies? Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and .Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Online Chat Rooms and In-site Communications
A submissives journey does make random checks of open chat room
logs and may periodically monitor open chat room conversations and
activities to ensure all activities are in accordance with Asj Guidelines
and in the best interest of the Asj Web Site and membership.  On
occasion, some of the logs of these conversations or discussions may be
posted on the Asj web site (for example, class or discussion logs).
Direct communication between individual site members (Private Messages
(PM's) and on site messaging (Site Messages) are not monitored and are
considered a mutually agreeable private conversation between the members
involved.  No attempt will be made to monitor the content or nature of
these conversations, however all members are reminded that such
conversations or messaging should only be done when all members
participating in the conversation are doing so willfully and voluntarily.
No member may insist that another member join them in that conversation, nor
should any member abuse this resource by sending continued unwarranted or
undesired messages. Members are reminded, it is against Asj policy to post
real life, personally identifying information (such as real names,
addresses, telephone numbers, etc.) in an open chat room forum.  Asj
does not maintain logs or recordings of video and audio chats.
Terms and Conditions Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.asubmissivesjourney.comYour Consent By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. http://www.asubmissivesjourney.com
privacy@asubmissivesjourney.com
Privacy Policy Created by Free Privacy Policy
